textmaster.com 2018-02-20

# Privacy Policy - TextMaster

In order to receive information about your Personal Data, the purposes and the parties the Data is shared with, contact the Owner. 

### Data Processing Ownership

TextMaster  
30 rue des Jeuneurs, 75002 Paris, France  
contact@textmaster.com

### Types of Data collected

The owner does not provide a list of Personal Data types collected. Other Personal Data collected may be highlighted by other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text, in the moment when the Data collection happens. 

The Personal Data may be freely inserted by the User or the Data Subject, or collected automatically when using the Application. 

Any use of Cookies by the Application or the owners of third party services used by the Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify the User and remember his/her preferences for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User. 

Failure to provide certain Personal Data, in particular Navigation Data, by deactivating the Application’s Cookies may make it impossible to surf or for the Application to provide its services. The Personal Data collected may regard both the User and third parties whose data the User provides. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through the Application and declares that (s)he has the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Owner of all responsibility towards third parties.

### Mode and Place of Processing the Data Obtained

###### METHOD OF PROCESSING

The Data Controller processes the Data of the Interested Parties and Users in a lawful and proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. Processing is carried out using computers and / or telematic means, with organizational methods and logics strictly related to the stated purposes. In addition to the owner, in some cases, access to the Data may be available to external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies). The updated list of Managers may be requested from the Owner at any time.

###### PLACE

The Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.

###### CONSERVATION TIME

The Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by the User, and the User can always ask for their suspension or removal.

### Additional Information About Data Processing

###### LEGAL PROTECTION

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner of the Application in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from its improper use or that of related services by the User.

###### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Specific information may be shown on the pages of the Site concerning particular services or the processing of Data provided by the User or by the Data Subject.

###### MAINTENANCE

The User’s Personal Data may be further used in ways and for purposes required for Application maintenance.

###### SYSTEM LOGS

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services it uses may collect system logs, i.e., files that record interaction – including navigation. They may also contain personal data, such as IP addresses.

###### INFORMATION NOT CONTAINED IN THIS POLICY

More information on processing Personal Information may be requested from the Owner at any time.

###### THE RIGHTS OF DATA SUBJECTS

Those persons to whom the Data refer have the right, at any time, to know whether their data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Owner of the Processing System.

###### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Application reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page, and by ensuring analogous protection of the Personal Information in all cases. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom.

###### DEFINITIONS AND LEGAL REFERENCES

Personal information or Data: Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

Browsing and Usage Data: Information collected automatically from the Site, including the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the users who connect to the site, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the visitor, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page) and the details about the path followed within the site with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the operating system and the user’s IT environment.

User: Means the individual user of the Application’s services or products.

Data Subject: The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refer.

Data Processor: The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other organization, association or organization designated by the Data Controller for the Personal Data processing system.

Data Controller: The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Site.

Last modified: February 18, 2014

TextMaster offers a professional online translation service that enables businesses to easily expand their international reach. By combining advanced technology with a network of verified expert translators in over 50 languages, TextMaster is redefining how businesses handle translation. Clients can access TextMaster through an online SaaS platform, API or a wide range of integrations and partners. More than 10,000 companies, from multinational corporations to SMBs, in 110 countries trust TextMaster to optimize their translation workflow.

Copyright 2017 © TextMaster.com - All rights reserved
